{
    "id": "97c511219ea149599c58bc2c21d2b400",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Smoking ....................................... on the campus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has forbidden",
                "has been forbidden"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "20e46b1a8494494589a94aa5e78a541e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Students ............................................ to smoke on the campus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have forbidden",
                "have been forbidden"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d937654c799a4492a7dddadc9b609d9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Consulting a good doctor ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "advised",
                "is advised"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c8607795f95c4bce9ba23c0cb581eb5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You .......................................... to consult a good doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "advised",
                "are advised"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "77fd17d6ccd8423898db690b87a4e094"
        },
        {
            "question": "Parking in front of their gate ........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is allowing",
                "allowed",
                "is allowed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "36de146b1e0c4396aab2c0f74e31f62b"
        },
        {
            "question": "People ......................................... to park in front of their gate.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are not allowing",
                "are not allowed",
                "not allowed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a023f242a21542359dba005c23ecacbb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Early booking .............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is advising",
                "advised",
                "is advised"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "afbd220eddc64570896f32b6e55cb39a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Passengers .......................................... to book their tickets early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "advised",
                "advising",
                "are advised"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "83d76afbfbe24811980059a748efb455"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was made ........................................... the whole story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "repeat",
                "to repeat"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "67d265b1f51e46aab0f009088918ca73"
        },
        {
            "question": "Pregnant women .......................................... to go on a diet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not advised",
                "are not advised",
                "are not advising"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2422ab0853bd473db1521916b432a514"
        }
    ]
}